[
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميـنـاتو 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ميناتو"
  } ,
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اورتشيمارو 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ر ت ش ي م ا ر و"
  },
{
  "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『لــوفـي 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ل و ف ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『مــايــكي 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ا ي ك ي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『روبيــن 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ر و ب ي ن"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ليـفـاي 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميـكاسـا 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ي ك ا س ا"
    },
    {
      "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غوجو ساتارو 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " غ و ج و س ا ت ا ر و"
    },
    {
      "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سوكونا 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س و ك و ن ا"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『البيغمام』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ب ي غ م ا م"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كايدو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ك ا ي د و"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اســـتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا س ت ا"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ايــزن』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ي ز ن"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سانيــمي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س ا ن ي م ي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا توميوكا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ه ا ش ي ر ات و م ي و ك ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا ميتسوري』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " ا ل ه ا ش ي ر ا م ي ت س و ر ي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سانـجي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س ا ن ج ي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوسوب』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و س و ب"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『شـانـكس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ش ا ن ك س"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميهـوك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ي ه و ك"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الشيطان موزان』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": " ا ل ش ي ط ا ن م و ز ا ن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي اكازا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ق م ر  ا ل ع ل و ي ا ك ا ز ا"
  },
  {
   "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『هـانكـوك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ه ا ن ك و ك"
  },
  { 
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سـاكورا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س ا ك و ر ا"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『شــادو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ش ا د و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا شينوبو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ه ا ش ي ر ا ش ي ن و ب و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي دوما』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ق م ر ا ل ع ل و  ي د و م ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي ككشيبو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ق م ر ا ل ع ل و  ي ك ك ش ي ب و"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『تانجيـرو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ت ا ن ج ي ر و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『نيـزوكو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ن ي ز و ك و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا رينجوكو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ه ا ش ي ر ا ر ي ن ج و ك و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها شيسوي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ش ي س و ي"
  },
  {
    "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها مادارا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا م ا د ا ر ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها ساسكي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا س ا س ك ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها ايتاتشي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ا ي ت  ا ت ش ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها اوبيتو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ا و ب ي ت و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ملك الدمار باين』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ل ك ا ل د م ا ر ب ا ي ن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جيرايا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『تسونادي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ت س و ن ا د ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ســـاي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س ا ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『تــوبي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ت و ب ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كــابـوتـو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ك ا ب و ت و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『بان ساما』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ب ا ن س ا م ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الاكاتسوي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ا ك ا ت س و ك ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غيـتو 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غ ي ت و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميـجـومي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ي ج و م ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يــوجي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ي و ج ي"
},
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『فيجيـتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ف ي ج ي ت ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『دانــزو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "د ا ن ز و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『شيـكامارو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ش ي ك ا م ا ر و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『لايــت』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ل ا ي ت"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『انيا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response":"ا ن ي ا "
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كــوبــي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ك و ب ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ديث نوت』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "د ي ث ن و ث"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كيــلوا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ك ي ل و ا"
    },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ون بيس عمك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "و ن ب ي س ع م ك"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ديمون استير』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "د ي م و ن ا س ت ي ر"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『دراغون بول』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "د ر ا غ و ن ب و ل"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『هيناتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ايـــمــا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ي م ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『دراكـــن』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "د ر ا ك ن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『 سونغ』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س و ن غ"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ماكيما』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ا ك ي م ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اكـاي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ك ا ي"
  },
  {    
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『السيد لوفي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل س ي د ل و ف ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوتشيها لوفي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ل و ف ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اوراهارا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كورابيكا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ك و ر ا ب ي ك ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『هيسوكا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ه ي س و ك ا"
  },
  {
 "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『إيلومي زولديك』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "إ ي ل و م ي ز و ل د ي ك"
  },
  {   
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جـون فريكس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ج و ن ف ر ي ك س"
},
{
  "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جيـن فريكس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ج ي ن ف ر ي ك س"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سـابــو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س ا ب و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ايـــس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ي س"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الادميرال كيزارو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ا د م ي ر ا ل ك ي ز ا ر و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『 اكاينو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ك ا ي ن و "
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الادميرال فيجيتورا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ا د م ي ر ا ل ف ي ج ي ت و ر ا"
  },
  {  
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الجيـروسي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ج ي ر و س ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『 تيتش』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ت ي ت ش"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الزباله غوكو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ز ب ا ل ه غ و ك و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『جـوهـــان』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ج و ه ا ن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『بيـــروس』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ب ي ر و س"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『زيـنو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ز ي ن و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميريوم』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ي ر ي و م"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ميناتـو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ي ن ا ت و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『بيــتو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ب ي ت و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『بــوف』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ب و ف"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يوسكي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ي و س ك ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اينوسكي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ي ن و س ك ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القمر العلوي ميتشيكاتسو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ق م ر ا ل ع ل و ي م ي ت ش ي ك ا ت س و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『القائد يامي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ق ا ئ د ي ا م ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غيــنيـا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غ ي ن ي ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『الهاشيرا هيمي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ه ا ش ي ر ا ه ي م ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『زينتســو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ز ي ن ت س و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كــانــاو』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ك ا ن ا و"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يوتا』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ي و ت ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『كاكاشي سينسي』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ك ا ك ا ش ي س ي ن س ي"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『يوهان』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ي و ه ا ن"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『سايتاما』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "س ا ي ت ا م ا"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『اللحيه البيضاء』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا ل ل ح ي ه ا ل ب ي ض ا ء"
  },
  {
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ادوارد نيوجت』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "ا د و ا ر د ن ي و ج ت"
  },
  {
  "question":"〘 ❖──── ~『ملك القراصنه 』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "م ل ك ا ل ق ر ا ص ن ه"
  },
  { 
"question":"〘 ❖──── ~『غول دي روجر』~────❖ 〙",
 "response": "غ و ل د ي ر و ج ر"
  }  
]